Lloyd: So now that you've
completed session three, it's
time to complete the relevant
section in the assessment booklet.
So if you can open your assessment
booklet and scroll down to  section
three, you will see there are five
questions within section three.
At the top, you have which question
relates to which, and also where
the information is in the course
materials if you need any assistance.
So for question one, it's asking
you in the box below, describe
the role of key organisations
in the cyber security industry.
So what are the organisations
involved in that?
What is their role?
What do they do?
For question two, it's asking you to
identify general job functions carried
out by cyber security professionals.
So what does a cyber security professional
do on their day to day and identify that.
So you can just list your responses there.
And for question three, it's asking
for a definition of the term hacking.
So what is hacking, what
does the term hacking mean?
And for question four, in the table
below it's asking you to explain the
difference between the following:
So what is a white hat hacker?
What is a black hat hacker?
And what is a grey hat hacker?
So it's an explain question, so try
and provide as much detail as your can.
So what does each of them do?
And what is the difference between them?
For the final question in this
assessment, it's asking you to
identify the key skill requirements
of a cyber security professional.
So what skills does a cyber
security professional need?
What would be of benefit to them?
What skills would be useful in their job?
Once you've done that, you can then save
the assessment, check through it, do a
spelling and grammar check, make sure
that you're happy with all your answers.
And then save that and submit
that to your tutor for marking.